[{"answer": "Well, we really think that he can do a lot of them.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "But how many of these will he actually do?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "The pledge, or the proposal, is to have China listed as a currency manipulator because they're not allowing their currency to float.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "I mean what -- it's all very well to say that, but what would President Romney, day one, actually do or say to China to carry through that pledge?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, Governor Romney has always said, you know, the point of going into business is to make the business successful which is defined at least, in part, by the business being able to make a profit.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, he's been saying those things already.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "The actual list of things which are to his credit, which Republicans never give him any credit for, is actually quite impressive if you highlight those pluses, isn't it?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Well, we should believe him because of the things that he's done in the first term.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "How would he get something out for this election and makes a series of further promises about what he will do in a second term, why should we believe him?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, that's why we have elections and often you get a second term.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "But what about the things that he promised to do that he then didn't do?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Lingerie model.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Which one do you prefer?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I'm not.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "It's much closer than I expected it to be.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "What do you think of the battle that we're now about to face?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "I love that I'm the authority of this because --", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Why is it -- why is it closer, do you think, than people expected?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, no, no, people come to me for their political insights.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Why shouldn't you be?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "I remember tweeting during one of the debates.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "I think the Republican race was just beyond comedic joy from start to finish, isn't it?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "It was very great.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "It was, isn't it?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "I -- Piers, I have spent over $10,000 on tickets so far.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Would you see that as a huge lottery to win?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I mean I think -- I think he is a businessman.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Do you buy into Mitt Romney's argument that he is a proven track record businessman and therefore he can run America like a successful company?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I would like my vagina to be taken off the table in the politics.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "What do you, as a smart woman in America, what do you want?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Well, it's been on the table.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Is it on the table?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "It could play both ways.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "It could play both ways, right?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "It's so adorable you think I was making a statement.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "The statement to George, to the nation, what were you doing in those pictures?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Yes, that's what we do.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Do you wake up in the morning and the first thing you do is head for BlackBerries, get the political news, start going at it?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "He's been talking about it all day.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, we're both reading.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "In bed?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, I'm reading the history of Islam and he's reading \"In Style\" magazine.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "What do you read?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "I'm fascinated by attachment parenting.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "You talk about attachment parenting?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "First of all, it was an extraordinary cover because the boy was, if I'm not mistaken, in camouflage pants.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What did you make of that cover, that extraordinary cover?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Is the glory coming your way in any way?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "ENTWORTH: No.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Yes, anything in it for you?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "No, he doesn't.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "He doesn't wake up, get the reigns (ph) and start beating his chest?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I beat my chest for him.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Doing his Tarzan impression?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Well, I mean --", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "But what do you think?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, I'm going to home-school them now after this.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "What do you want for your kids?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "You know, I'm very excited.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "How excited are you about London?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "No, I never give up.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "-- hundredth of a second, you just give up?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I broke my thumb in the next race, yes.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "You really broke your thumb hitting a wall?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "I was just -- I can't -- I couldn't believe that I lost by a touch.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Because you were so full of rage?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I didn't know I did it.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "How hard are you hitting that wall to break your thumb?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Having my daughter.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Is there any experience in the world better than winning a gold medal at the Olympics, that you've enjoyed yourself?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Which one are you going to take?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yes, something like that.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "I've got your mind racing back to some -- I don't know, where are we going, a beach?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I'm going to have to shut my mouth more.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "See, I always quaintly assumed that when you get to that stage of the preparation, it's like boxers.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "There are like --", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Anyone on the American Olympic squad that you think?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I'm as old as their mothers.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "You might be the lucky recipient of my joy?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "No, we're not.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Are we going to stand side by side and do it together?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Well, people have to remember I do this for a living.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "How do you keep that six-pack looking like that?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Probably between four and six hours.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "For how long?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I've just done a very thorough research job on you.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Where do you get your information from?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "No, I -- he's great.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "So did you fire him?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "I don't like to share because I don't want to jinx anything.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "What has he said about London?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "And hundreds of millions of people around the world.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "It'll stay between us?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "He's gotten a lot right about my personal life.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "What has he got right?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Well, I -- well, OK.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "He predicted you would have a daughter?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Well, what you do is you go in there and he leaves the room, and you take a card, and you write down three questions that you want answered, and you write down three people that have passed away, and you sign and print your name.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Who do you talk to?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "My dad.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Which relatives, if you don't mind me asking?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Yes, my dad, who passed away.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Who've passed away?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "I don't have a conversation.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "And you have, what, a conversation through this -- ?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Well, I guess I'll find out in a few months.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "Or is the first love really in that water, winning, until that's done in your life, do you think you've got a chance of -- ?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "I feel like when I'm ready to move on, like my dad said, is be more family oriented and settle down.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "I mean, do you feel that you're -- ?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "I actually would just like to make the Olympic team.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "The one last gold in London?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "You will, won't you?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "Susan?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "Well, I've said over and over again that over 30 years, 33 years, they've just gone from one breaking case event to another breaking case event to another.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 779, "question": "What do you think they'll be feeling tonight?", "qSentId": 778}, {"answer": "I think that they have certainly gone very far down a road of being able to know how to track children.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "Do you think that?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "Have you had a favorite guest over the years besides me?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "No, but -- and he can have my job.", "docId": "120524pmt", "aSentId": 843, "question": "You don't think he's going to do the news for the rest of his life, do you?", "qSentId": 842}]